Emmaline Salles

www.linkedin.com/in/emmalinesalles | www.github.com/emmalinekay

I have over 2 years of experience in the marketing and sales industry. However, my experience in the tech industry inspired me to take on a new challenge and learn how to code. I'm constantly looking for new experiences and knowledge that will better me as a person and professional.

Fort Lauderdale, Florida (201) 755-7635 emmalinesalles@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Worldox, New Jersey — Marketing & Sales Assistant

NOV 2016- JUN 2017

- Ran Social Media pages & assisted with planning trade shows.
- Assisted the Sales Manager by providing high-level customer service and support with product expertise and advanced selling skills.

NimbleStack, New York — *Marketing Associate*

MAR 2016 - JUL 2016

- Managed various Social Media accounts. Designed content and led development team for the creation of two websites.
- Developed numerous conversational flow charts and created business plans for different chat bots.

Restorando, Buenos Aires — Junior Communications Analyst

AUG 2015 - JAN 2016

- Main contact for both Social Media and PR agencies: Final decision making on all social media posts in Argentina, Chile, Colombia, and Peru. Co-organizer of press events.
- Head of Trade Marketing: Responsible for distribution of POP material in the entire Latin American region.

Mars Marketing, New Jersey — Marketing Intern

MAY 2014 - JUL 2014

- Wrote blogs for websites; created mail out flyers for different clients; assisted in production for a nightlife event, served as a Spanish translator and assisted with any other everyday tasks.

EDUCATION

Ironhack, Miami — Full Stack Web Development (400+hours)

AUGUST 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

Technologies: JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Angular 2, Node.js, Express, MongoDB

Universidad Torcuato Ditella, Buenos Aires — *International Studies*

JANUARY 2010 - MAY 2015

Attended UNC Chapel Hill for Spring Semester of 2014

New York University, New York — *Marketing Practices and Principles*JUNE 2014 - AUGUST 2014

One of the courses of NYU's Summer Sessions program.

PROJECTS

Bounce

JavaScript Ball game that changes colors with a click. Uses JavaScript, JQuery, SCSS, HTML, CSS

Brito's List

Web application that stores contact information for networking purposes. Uses JavaScript, NodeJS, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, PassportJS, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Heroku

Bibix

A Beer Recommendation app. Uses Angular 2, typeScript, JavaScript, jQuery, NodeJS, MongoDB, Express, HTML, SASS, Bootstrap,

BrewBot

Winning Idea of AB-InBev's BrewHacks Hackathon 2016. I was responsible for content development, research, and design.

CERTIFICATES/ADDT'L STUDIES

Scene Study II w/ Jon Korkes Stella Adler Studio - 2016

10 week Acting Introductory Program Stella Adler Studio – 2016

4 week Acting-For-Film New York Film Academy - 2015

International Baccalaureate Diploma St. Matthew's College - 2010

Digital Marketing SpecializationUniversity of Illinois - Online via
Coursera - ongoing

LANGUAGES

English (1st native); Spanish (2nd native); French (conversation/reading); Latin (High School level)